<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Wisdom Vision</string>
    <string name="name" translatable="false">Wisdom Vision</string>
    <string name="account">Account(Phone Number)</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="input_new_password">Input new password</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone number</string>
    <string name="email">e-mail</string>
    <string name="input_new_email">Input new Email</string>
    <string name="username">User Name</string>
    <string name="input_new_username">Input new username</string>
    <string name="isVisuallyImpaired">Is visually impaired</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log in</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log out</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="close_account">Close account</string>
    <string name="check_of_close_account">Are you sure to close account?</string>
    <string name="repeat">Repeat Password</string>
    <string name="input_email">Input e-mail</string>
    <string name="input_password">Input Password</string>
    <string name="input_phone_num">Input Phone Number</string>
    <string name="input_user_name">Input Your Name</string>
    <string name="user_setting">User Data Setting</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="change_user_name">change User Name</string>
    <string name="change_email">Change e-mail</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="home_page">Home Page</string>
    <string name="setting_page">Setting</string>
    <string name="Route_HomePage" translatable="false">HomePage</string>
    <string name="Route_SettingPage" translatable="false">SettingPage</string>
    <string name="signup_page">Sign up</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect us</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="other_set">Others Setting</string>
    <string name="change_language">Change Language</string>
    <string name="toggle_password_visibility">Toggle Password Visibility</string>
    <string name="chinese" translatable="false">中文</string>
    <string name="english" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="japanese" translatable="false">日本語</string>
    <string name="french" translatable="false">Français</string>
    <string name="korean" translatable="false">한국어</string>
    <string name="language_selection">Language Selection</string>
    <string name="request">need help</string>
    <string name="list">help list</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="Route_ListPage" translatable="false">HelpListPage</string>
    <string name="Route_FriendList" translatable="false">RequestPage</string>
    <string name="Route_LoggingPage" translatable="false">LoginPage</string>
    <string name="Route_RequestPage" translatable="false">RequestPage</string>
    <string name="check_of_Log_out">Are you sure to Log Out?</string>
    <string name="Client">Client</string>
    <string name="Description">Detail description</string>
    <string name="Location">Location</string>
    <string name="completed">Client has confirmed the commission is completed.</string>
    <string name="thank">Thanks for you help</string>
    <string name="hint1">We will identify it for you, please stay still for five seconds.</string>
    <string name="hint2">Please point the camera towards the ground and remain still for five seconds.</string>
    <string name="wait">Recognizing, please wait</string>
    <string name="notification_title">Visually impaired people need assistance</string>
    <string name="no_help">There are currently no visually impaired persons in need of assistance.</string>
    <string name="introduce1">Hello and welcome to Wisdom Vision! Next, I will give you a brief introduction to how to use the APP.</string>
    <string name="introduce_isV2">On the main screen, you will see two main buttons: one is located in the upper right corner, click to enter the settings page; the other is located in the lower center of the screen, click to activate the voice recognition function. After activation, you can ask questions on your phone and we will provide assistance based on your questions. The voice recognition function will automatically stop after 30 seconds, so you don\'t have to worry about it while listening to your voice. In addition, after finishing speaking the question, you can also press the recognition button again to end the voice recognition immediately.</string>
    <string name="introduce_isV3">"General identification function You can ask questions, such as: \"Is there a pen in front of you?\" The APP will activate the camera for identification. To ensure recognition accuracy, please keep your phone steady for about 5 seconds to allow the camera to capture the image. The recognition results will be played by voice and displayed in the answer box above the recognition button. "</string>
    <string name="introduce_isV4">"Continuous recognition function When the question contains the keyword \"Follow\" (such as \"I want to pay attention to whether the pen is in sight?\"), The app will continue to turn on the camera to identify whether there are items or people you are paying attention to until you ask again or exit the APP. The identification results are presented in the same way as general identification. "</string>
    <string name="introduce2">When your mobile phone receives a notification, it means that a visually impaired person needs help, and you are the nearest helper. Enter the APP to know the name and location of the visually impaired person. Please also try to reach the non-visually impaired person as quickly as possible. location and provide assistance. If you are willing to become a facilitator, you can click the button in the lower right corner to enter the main page and start using the APP. If you don\'t want to, click the button in the lower left corner and it will return you to the login page.</string>
    <string name="introduce_isV5">Emergency assistance function When the question contains the keyword \"need help\" (such as \"I need help, I\'m lost\"), the APP will activate the camera to identify your location. Please point the phone lens towards the ground and keep it steady for about 5 seconds. We will send your needs and location to the nearest facilitator. When it is confirmed that a helper is coming, the APP will inform you with a voice that \"xxx is coming and will provide assistance, please wait\", and the result will also be displayed in the answer box.</string>
    <string name="introduce_isV6">The instructions end here. You can click the button in the lower right corner to enter the main page and start using the APP.</string>
    <string name="introduce_isV7">If you have any questions about the function, you can click the button in the screen to listen to the instructions again. If you need to listen to the instructions again later, go to the Help button on the settings page. Thank you for listening in detail.</string>
    <string name="introduce3">Hello and welcome to Wisdom Vision! There are 7 buttons on this page, namely full introduction, main screen button function introduction, general identification function introduction, continuous identification function introduction, emergency assistance function introduction and function question introduction. You can choose to listen to the one that suits you at your own time. introduction. If you are not interested in the instructions or already know how to use Wisdom Vision, you can click the button in the lower right corner to enter the main page and start using the APP.</string>
    <string name="common_I">General identification function</string>
    <string name="continue_I">Continuous recognition function</string>
    <string name="emergency_I">Emergency assistance function</string>
    <string name="questionI">questions about the function</string>
    <string name="all_I">All introduction</string>
    <string name="button_I">Home screen button functions</string>
    <string name="permission_request">permission request</string>
    <string name="introduce4">If you need to review the help again later, go to the Help button on the settings page and click it. Thank you for your detailed viewing.</string>
</resources>